<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin, Author at News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://somaira.vercel.app/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/author/admin/</link>
	<description>News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:34:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A homeless dog who has only two legs protected his puppies and changed his life in the process</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/a-homeless-dog-who-has-only-two-legs-protected-his-puppies-and-changed-his-life-in-the-process/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/a-homeless-dog-who-has-only-two-legs-protected-his-puppies-and-changed-his-life-in-the-process/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of the incredible dog Shi Bao from China, whose fate has become known throughout the world. She used to have a family. But for... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/a-homeless-dog-who-has-only-two-legs-protected-his-puppies-and-changed-his-life-in-the-process/">A homeless dog who has only two legs protected his puppies and changed his life in the process</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of the incredible dog Shi Bao from China, whose fate has become known throughout the world.</p>
<p>She used to have a family. But for some reason, the owners decided to abandon her, leaving her near the railroad tracks.</p>
<p>That’s where Shi Bao lost her hind legs. Locals say she was run over by a train.</p>
<p>But our heroine proved to be a real fighter.She would not give up and even brought a wonderful offspring into this world. Four adorable puppies became her life’s meaning.</p>
<p>Photo: kotopediya.com<br />
The heroine’s story was told in the local Internet publications, and it immediately went viral and flew around the world.</p>
<p>And the rescue organization AnimalsAsia.org, learning about Shi Bao, set out to find her.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/a-homeless-dog-who-has-only-two-legs-protected-his-puppies-and-changed-his-life-in-the-process/">A homeless dog who has only two legs protected his puppies and changed his life in the process</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/a-homeless-dog-who-has-only-two-legs-protected-his-puppies-and-changed-his-life-in-the-process/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orphaned raccoon rescued by family with dogs now thinks he’s a dog too</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/orphaned-raccoon-rescued-by-family-with-dogs-now-thinks-hes-a-dog-too/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/orphaned-raccoon-rescued-by-family-with-dogs-now-thinks-hes-a-dog-too/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The girl was named Pamkin and she gets along well with family members and their pets. Washing brooks and dog. Source: storyfox.com Rosie Kemp discovered a baby raccoon... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/orphaned-raccoon-rescued-by-family-with-dogs-now-thinks-hes-a-dog-too/">Orphaned raccoon rescued by family with dogs now thinks he’s a dog too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The girl was named Pamkin and she gets along well with family members and their pets.</p>
<p>Washing brooks and dog. Source: storyfox.com<br />
Rosie Kemp discovered a baby raccoon near her house about a year ago that had apparently fallen from a tree. It was all alone, so Rosie and her daughter Laura brought the baby home. The baby was named Pamkin. The orphaned raccoon quickly recovered, settled down and stayed with its rescuers.</p>
<p>Wash Creek. Source: storyfox.com<br />
Laura says that her raccoon girl quickly found a common language with her family and the two dogs that live at home. She goes everywhere with them and has generally started acting like a dog! Pamkin loves to play, she is very affectionate and gentle, but if she doesn’t like something she growls to show her displeasure.</p>
<p>Washbays and dog. Source: storyfox.com<br />
This is how the tame raccoon Rosie found with a broken leg in the backyard looks now.</p>
<p>Pumkin can pet and growl, but she is respectful of family members and her four-legged friends</p>
<p>Washbays and dog. Source: storyfox.com<br />
Taking care of her is not the easiest task, but very gratifying</p>
<p>Rumpkin is a very smart puppy and also incredibly emotional, so you never get bored with her!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/orphaned-raccoon-rescued-by-family-with-dogs-now-thinks-hes-a-dog-too/">Orphaned raccoon rescued by family with dogs now thinks he’s a dog too</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/orphaned-raccoon-rescued-by-family-with-dogs-now-thinks-hes-a-dog-too/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Their favorite place was the peaks of Penn and Fen in Wales, where they went together for years</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/their-favorite-place-was-the-peaks-of-penn-and-fen-in-wales-where-they-went-together-for-years/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/their-favorite-place-was-the-peaks-of-penn-and-fen-in-wales-where-they-went-together-for-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pets are part of the family. It is difficult when we have to separate from them, and when this man found out that his dog would not live... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/their-favorite-place-was-the-peaks-of-penn-and-fen-in-wales-where-they-went-together-for-years/">Their favorite place was the peaks of Penn and Fen in Wales, where they went together for years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pets are part of the family. It is difficult when we have to separate from them, and when this man found out that his dog would not live long, he decided to take him in a wheelchair to his favorite place for the last time.</p>
<p>Saying goodbye to a longtime pet is like saying goodbye to a family member. These emotional photos show how the owner of the dog last decided to drive his pet in a stroller to his favorite place in the mountains.</p>
<p>During their ten-year stay together, the dog Labrador Monti enjoyed exploring the hills and mountain peaks with its owner Carlos Fresco. Their favorite place was the peaks of Penn and Fen in Wales, where they went together for years.</p>
<p>Carlos says he knew their long-term friendship ended after Monty was re-diagnosed with cancer. The little hero struggled with a serious illness for 18 months, and his owner, wanting to please him, decided to take him to his favorite place for the last time.</p>
<p>Since Monty was very exhausted from the disease and could not climb the steep paths on his own, Carlos drove him in a construction cart this time. Monty died on June 21 while lying on his owner’s bed, and Carlos had to hide the sad news from other family members so as not to spoil their day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/their-favorite-place-was-the-peaks-of-penn-and-fen-in-wales-where-they-went-together-for-years/">Their favorite place was the peaks of Penn and Fen in Wales, where they went together for years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/their-favorite-place-was-the-peaks-of-penn-and-fen-in-wales-where-they-went-together-for-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Pudu ἱs the mσst beautἱful and smartest deer in the wσrld</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/the-pudu-%e1%bc%b1s-the-m%cf%83st-beaut%e1%bc%b1ful-and-smartest-deer-in-the-w%cf%83rld/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/the-pudu-%e1%bc%b1s-the-m%cf%83st-beaut%e1%bc%b1ful-and-smartest-deer-in-the-w%cf%83rld/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I had never heard of this kind of deer before! On May 12, 2015, a baby was born at the New York City Bird’s Zoo. When she passed... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/the-pudu-%e1%bc%b1s-the-m%cf%83st-beaut%e1%bc%b1ful-and-smartest-deer-in-the-w%cf%83rld/">The Pudu ἱs the mσst beautἱful and smartest deer in the wσrld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I had never heard of this kind of deer before! On May 12, 2015, a baby was born at the New York City Bird’s Zoo. When she passed away, the small pudu weighed less than a pound and was 6 inches tall.</p>
<p>The pudu is the smallest deer in the world, and it is only found in Argentina and Chile, where it is thought to be extint. When a young deer was let out of a zoo, the story went viral, and I can see why.</p>
<p>About 10 days after the deer was borned, a visitor to the zoo took a picture of it and posted it on the zoo’s Facebook page.</p>
<p>Isn’t he precious?</p>
<p>The deer is nursing, but she is starting to eat some greens, kale, and carrots. When he gets bigger, the white spots will fall off, which won’t be very noticeable. The adults in the park stood up a foot tall</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/the-pudu-%e1%bc%b1s-the-m%cf%83st-beaut%e1%bc%b1ful-and-smartest-deer-in-the-w%cf%83rld/">The Pudu ἱs the mσst beautἱful and smartest deer in the wσrld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/the-pudu-%e1%bc%b1s-the-m%cf%83st-beaut%e1%bc%b1ful-and-smartest-deer-in-the-w%cf%83rld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee-2/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Some cute pictures show the close relationship between Do Do, a two-year-old chimpanzee, and Aorp, a two-month-old tiger cub. It’s true that chimpanzees can have a stooped posture... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee-2/">Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some cute pictures show the close relationship between Do Do, a two-year-old chimpanzee, and Aorp, a two-month-old tiger cub. It’s true that chimpanzees can have a stooped posture just like hippos, and this cute picture proves it.</p>
<p>As seen on BuzzFeed and Neatorama, a two-year-old chimp named Do Do holds a tiger cub named Aorp in her arms and feeds her with a milk bottle.</p>
<p>Every time the music stops, Do Do puts the bottle in her mouth, just like a human mother would do to see if her baby is ready for milk.</p>
<p>The baby tiger and the ape are so used to each other that the ape’s motherly instincts take over as she feeds it from a bottle. Aorp slurps up the milk happily while Do Do carefully holds the tiger in her arms.</p>
<p>Do Do is wearing a pair of denim shorts for some unexplained reason, maybe to protect her thighs from Aorp’s claws.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee-2/">Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mἱgalσσ ἱs the σnly whἱte humpbacƙ whale ἱn the wσrld</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/m%e1%bc%b1gal%cf%83%cf%83-%e1%bc%b1s-the-%cf%83nly-wh%e1%bc%b1te-humpbac%c6%99-whale-%e1%bc%b1n-the-w%cf%83rld/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/m%e1%bc%b1gal%cf%83%cf%83-%e1%bc%b1s-the-%cf%83nly-wh%e1%bc%b1te-humpbac%c6%99-whale-%e1%bc%b1n-the-w%cf%83rld/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=206</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We accept prejudice in all its forms because, as humans, we are part of it and couldn’t live without it. On the other hand, nature tends to surprise... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/m%e1%bc%b1gal%cf%83%cf%83-%e1%bc%b1s-the-%cf%83nly-wh%e1%bc%b1te-humpbac%c6%99-whale-%e1%bc%b1n-the-w%cf%83rld/">Mἱgalσσ ἱs the σnly whἱte humpbacƙ whale ἱn the wσrld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We accept prejudice in all its forms because, as humans, we are part of it and couldn’t live without it. On the other hand, nature tends to surprise us with its oddities.</p>
<p>On this particular occasion, paint was used to “paint” a humpback whale. Because of its unusual head, a whale called Migaloo is a very rare species.</p>
<p>This humpback whale is the only one in the world that is white. Think about how lucky you are that you can see him. In fact, a few lucky people were able to take pictures of the whale while sailing near Sydney, Australia. This is one chance in a million to see Migaloo in the sea.</p>
<p>This giant was caught for the first time in 1991. The whale has gone a long way in a short amount of time. This beautiful whale is 31 years old. Biologists say that this breed can live for up.</p>
<p>Let’s not forget that the word “white guy” is where Migaloo comes from.</p>
<p>Even so, no one knows what makes the animal’s skin white. He could be a real albipo or have leucemia.</p>
<p>Source: https://dailylifeworld.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/m%e1%bc%b1gal%cf%83%cf%83-%e1%bc%b1s-the-%cf%83nly-wh%e1%bc%b1te-humpbac%c6%99-whale-%e1%bc%b1n-the-w%cf%83rld/">Mἱgalσσ ἱs the σnly whἱte humpbacƙ whale ἱn the wσrld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/m%e1%bc%b1gal%cf%83%cf%83-%e1%bc%b1s-the-%cf%83nly-wh%e1%bc%b1te-humpbac%c6%99-whale-%e1%bc%b1n-the-w%cf%83rld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seal ἱs very happy tσ see hἱs Mἱpἱare Self Tσy and hσlds ἱt tἱghtly</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/seal-%e1%bc%b1s-very-happy-t%cf%83-see-h%e1%bc%b1s-m%e1%bc%b1p%e1%bc%b1are-self-t%cf%83y-and-h%cf%83lds-%e1%bc%b1t-t%e1%bc%b1ghtly/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/seal-%e1%bc%b1s-very-happy-t%cf%83-see-h%e1%bc%b1s-m%e1%bc%b1p%e1%bc%b1are-self-t%cf%83y-and-h%cf%83lds-%e1%bc%b1t-t%e1%bc%b1ghtly/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=203</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seals are cute little creatures that live mostly in water. I’ve seen a lot of beautiful pictures of these animals on social media. A baby seal is looking... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/seal-%e1%bc%b1s-very-happy-t%cf%83-see-h%e1%bc%b1s-m%e1%bc%b1p%e1%bc%b1are-self-t%cf%83y-and-h%cf%83lds-%e1%bc%b1t-t%e1%bc%b1ghtly/">Seal ἱs very happy tσ see hἱs Mἱpἱare Self Tσy and hσlds ἱt tἱghtly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seals are cute little creatures that live mostly in water. I’ve seen a lot of beautiful pictures of these animals on social media. A baby seal is looking at the photographer. A happy baby seal is grinning at the camera.</p>
<p>When a well-behaved adult seal walks into a fish market, he asks for his food. These photos may always make Internet users smile or laugh out loud, even in these uncertain times. Who can say no to a baby’s pure sweetness?</p>
<p>The pictures that come next will also make you feel good. A seal is very happy to get a toy that looks just like it. He couldn’t stop playing with his toy, which showed how much he loved it. This is likely the coolest thing he’s learned so far.</p>
<p>The seal’s beautiful appearance reminds us of how happy we are when we get a gift we really like. A pleasant surprise that makes even the hardest of hearts soften. Sometimes, that’s all it takes to get lucky.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/seal-%e1%bc%b1s-very-happy-t%cf%83-see-h%e1%bc%b1s-m%e1%bc%b1p%e1%bc%b1are-self-t%cf%83y-and-h%cf%83lds-%e1%bc%b1t-t%e1%bc%b1ghtly/">Seal ἱs very happy tσ see hἱs Mἱpἱare Self Tσy and hσlds ἱt tἱghtly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/seal-%e1%bc%b1s-very-happy-t%cf%83-see-h%e1%bc%b1s-m%e1%bc%b1p%e1%bc%b1are-self-t%cf%83y-and-h%cf%83lds-%e1%bc%b1t-t%e1%bc%b1ghtly/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peσple are surprἱsed tσ see three whἱte-tailed deer grazἱng tσgether ἱn a fἱeld</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/pe%cf%83ple-are-surpr%e1%bc%b1sed-t%cf%83-see-three-wh%e1%bc%b1te-tailed-deer-graz%e1%bc%b1ng-t%cf%83gether-%e1%bc%b1n-a-f%e1%bc%b1eld/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/pe%cf%83ple-are-surpr%e1%bc%b1sed-t%cf%83-see-three-wh%e1%bc%b1te-tailed-deer-graz%e1%bc%b1ng-t%cf%83gether-%e1%bc%b1n-a-f%e1%bc%b1eld/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The three white stags were seen mating with dogs in the Hertfordshire fields. This kind of mating between animals is called leucism. A white stag’s head was taken... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/pe%cf%83ple-are-surpr%e1%bc%b1sed-t%cf%83-see-three-wh%e1%bc%b1te-tailed-deer-graz%e1%bc%b1ng-t%cf%83gether-%e1%bc%b1n-a-f%e1%bc%b1eld/">Peσple are surprἱsed tσ see three whἱte-tailed deer grazἱng tσgether ἱn a fἱeld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The three white stags were seen mating with dogs in the Hertfordshire fields. This kind of mating between animals is called leucism. A white stag’s head was taken after it was found on Exmoor in 2007. Seeing a lone white stag is pretty rare, but seeing three of them at once is like something out of a fairy tale.</p>
<p>This family of three was seen grazing with their dogs in the fields of Hertfordshire. White stags are rarely seen in the wild because their way of mating is controlled by a trait called leucism. Because they look like ghosts, they are easy prey for tгoрһу һᴜпteгѕ.</p>
<p>The three white stags were seen grazing with the dogs in the Hertfordshire fields. What the people who broke it said could be another story. People believe that if they end the life of a white stag, they will be cursed for the rest of their lives.</p>
<p>In fact, they already did. They have been shown as messengers from beyond the grave or as guides from the spirit world. So far, they have been in The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe by C.S. Lewis, The Hobbit by J.R.R. Tolkien, and J.K. Rowling’s Harry Potter books.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/pe%cf%83ple-are-surpr%e1%bc%b1sed-t%cf%83-see-three-wh%e1%bc%b1te-tailed-deer-graz%e1%bc%b1ng-t%cf%83gether-%e1%bc%b1n-a-f%e1%bc%b1eld/">Peσple are surprἱsed tσ see three whἱte-tailed deer grazἱng tσgether ἱn a fἱeld</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/pe%cf%83ple-are-surpr%e1%bc%b1sed-t%cf%83-see-three-wh%e1%bc%b1te-tailed-deer-graz%e1%bc%b1ng-t%cf%83gether-%e1%bc%b1n-a-f%e1%bc%b1eld/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Some cute pictures show the close relationship between Do Do, a two-year-old chimpanzee, and Aorp, a two-month-old tiger cub. It’s true that chimpanzees can have a stooped posture... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee/">Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some cute pictures show the close relationship between Do Do, a two-year-old chimpanzee, and Aorp, a two-month-old tiger cub. It’s true that chimpanzees can have a stooped posture just like hippos, and this cute picture proves it.</p>
<p>As seen on BuzzFeed and Neatorama, a two-year-old chimp named Do Do holds a tiger cub named Aorp in her arms and feeds her with a milk bottle.</p>
<p>Every time the music stops, Do Do puts the bottle in her mouth, just like a human mother would do to see if her baby is ready for milk.</p>
<p>The baby tiger and the ape are so used to each other that the ape’s motherly instincts take over as she feeds it from a bottle. Aorp slurps up the milk happily while Do Do carefully holds the tiger in her arms.</p>
<p>Do Do is wearing a pair of denim shorts for some unexplained reason, maybe to protect her thighs from Aorp’s claws.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee/">Twσ-mσnth-σld tἱger cub gets mἱlƙ from Dσ Dσ a twσ-year-σld chἱmpanzee</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/tw%cf%83-m%cf%83nth-%cf%83ld-t%e1%bc%b1ger-cub-gets-m%e1%bc%b1l%c6%99-from-d%cf%83-d%cf%83-a-tw%cf%83-year-%cf%83ld-ch%e1%bc%b1mpanzee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sick Woman Says Goodbye to Her Beloved Horse And Dogs For The Last Time From Her Hospice Bed</title>
		<link>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/sick-woman-says-goodbye-to-her-beloved-horse-and-dogs-for-the-last-time-from-her-hospice-bed-2/</link>
					<comments>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/sick-woman-says-goodbye-to-her-beloved-horse-and-dogs-for-the-last-time-from-her-hospice-bed-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[animal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://somaira.vercel.app/?p=194</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jan Holman is a 68-year-old woman who used to live in a hospital but now stays at the Hospice of the Good Shepherd in Chester, England. She is... </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/sick-woman-says-goodbye-to-her-beloved-horse-and-dogs-for-the-last-time-from-her-hospice-bed-2/">Sick Woman Says Goodbye to Her Beloved Horse And Dogs For The Last Time From Her Hospice Bed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jan Holman is a 68-year-old woman who used to live in a hospital but now stays at the Hospice of the Good Shepherd in Chester, England. She is very sick and her life will soon come to an end. She got all the attention she needed, but she missed her horses Bob and Monty and Rowley and her dogs Monty and Rowley.</p>
<p>The woman said that Bob was a very important part of her life and that she had been riding him up until the day before she went to the hospital. After seeing Jan’s trouble, the staff decided to surprise her by adding her three animal friends to the list of guests. This led to a happy get-together. The staff at the hospice finished getting ready before taking Jan to the entrance to the courtyard to give him the sweet surprise.</p>
<p>Jan knew that her horse was hers. When he got there, the people who work at the Thornleigh Park Farm Stables, where Bob lives freely, were with him. Even though she couldn’t get out of bed, the woman’s face showed that she was happy, especially when she thought about the chance of seeing Bob again. Bob sat on Jan’s lap and immediately stroked her neck, putting his head through the door so that Jan could touch him.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/sick-woman-says-goodbye-to-her-beloved-horse-and-dogs-for-the-last-time-from-her-hospice-bed-2/">Sick Woman Says Goodbye to Her Beloved Horse And Dogs For The Last Time From Her Hospice Bed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://somaira.vercel.app/">News</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://somaira.vercel.app/2022/12/14/sick-woman-says-goodbye-to-her-beloved-horse-and-dogs-for-the-last-time-from-her-hospice-bed-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
